Seino! Galgal Channel GOGO!
Yes, so today we have the popular TikTok dance competition.
Is this a team competition? Yes, we will be splitting into two teams and playing against each other in a team competition.
TikTok is a bit difficult these days, isn't it? It's not at all.
Yes, I graduated from TikTokker. You're a TikTokker now?
I was a TikTokker until last year. But it was rather recently.
I graduated, so I'm not sure.
Let's all do our best.
Is that okay?
Yes, I'm good.
Let's see, let's see if we can figure it out with a good bar.
Oh, no, that's not good.
Let's split up.
We're splitting up.
It's not TikTokker. I'm not a TikTokker.
I don't want to be tied down too much. I don't want to be tied down too much. I don't want to be tied down too much.
I don't know where I'm going, but I'm not sure if it's a rest day or what I usually do when I'm on TikTokker.
I'm going to be a tick-tocker for one more round.
I'm going to be a tick tocker... and I think I've got a line.
Who's the longest? - Yes.
I wonder who's been here the longest.
I'm just hoping that I can dance somehow. If I can dance better than the other team, I win.
Then, I'm confident at once. I can see your confidence.
We are divided, aren't we?
What are you going to do if you lose?
You didn't say that.
No.
No, I don't want to.
Then, do you want to make a funny face and do a waiting list?
I'll make a funny face.
Scribble on your face.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Then we'll do that for anyone and everyone. If we lose.
I'll do it in Macau with you.
Miyu Chiyori
If we lose, we'll do a doodle location.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
As long as we don't lose.
Just the four of us.
Just a minute.
Let's start the video.
Okay, let's get started, shall we?
Yes, please.
Okay, let's start with the number of people who got to dance.
That would be great.
That's the best one. It seems more equal.
Let's see how many people can dance.
Oh, no.
I'm so nervous.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go!
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm not going to answer it.
Wait a minute.
It's coming out.
Oh!
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
Hold the hot water.
Just now.
You just said how many people were in there.
Actually, there were three of us, and we were fast.
How many?
They all danced.
One point.
Is this the Pokemon one?
This is not fast.
I'll take this one, please.
Next...
Atsuna and Tsunatsu
I have no idea.
You don't!
You just know!
No, I don't.
But there it is.
The three of you are together.
Why am I doing this?
We won by one!
Thanks!
Next...
I'm off!
Wow!
How do you do that?
You're doing it!
Whoa!
Come on!
Isn't this how it's supposed to be done?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Go, go, go!
Whoa!
How do you do that?
I got this.
You dropped!
Why? I didn't hear the song.
Too loud.
Well, then, we have a tie.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's great, Mo-chan.
What was that?
Isn't it this one?
But it went right in, didn't it? That's it.
You're in good company.
Yuzu.
Just yuzu.
He's so fired up.
Like you're the only one who lost?
It's a team competition.
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
You did this?
You saw the video.
I can't lose.
Please do.
What? How?
What's this?
Someone's getting better.
Wait!
I don't know, but this...
This is different.
This isn't it.
No, no, no
Charming.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's okay.
Okay, Shibuya.
I'm quitting.
I know because I did it.
Can you dance once?
How's it going?
I don't remember.
We did it together.
Take a look.
So these are the points?
No points.
Three against two.
That's hard.
Two against two.
What's wrong?
Hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mm.
mmm
Mm-hmm.
Yes, yes, hangers on. The cat is walking.
I feel like I'm pretending a little bit differently.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, I got it.
And the cat was walking.
Oh, this is all I got.
This was done.
The cat.
The cat was doing it.
This is amazing.
But...
Anyway...
I'll do it.
I'll do my best.
Oh, it's a tie.
It's a tie.
Oh, now it's a tie.
Tie.
Tie
Hmmm...
That's that one, isn't it?
I know a little bit about it, but I don't know.
Rimic.
This is difficult.
You're so good!
This is hard.
I can't do it
I know, I know, I know.
What's wrong?
I'm the only one who knows.
What's going on?
What is it? What's this?
What is it? What is this?
Oh, that's great.
I've been trying.
You got it, didn't you?
I thought something was wrong.
That was a great performance by a middle-aged man.
That's great.
You did great.
Let's go for it.
For now.
I'll think about it after we get out of here.
I'll think about it when I get out
I'm not afraid of anything
This will come out someday. You'll see.
Eight of us took it.
So it's four against four, four against five.
Four against five. That's right. Sorry.
Four against five.
I don't get this one.
Oh, this is it.
Really?
I'll give it a try.
Is this right?
Yes, it's right.
Are you sure?
Let's do a little video scene.
Shall we do it?
It's supposed to be really cool.
What? Isn't it supposed to be like this?
What is this?
It's a little bit mixed up.
It's not right, is it?
Excuse me.
Can I try again?
No. Why not?
Okay, now what?
Three, two, one, go!
It's like they're trying to match the pillars.
That's great.
It's a little different.
You mean there's this version, too?
I see.
It's my first time.
I couldn't give it away, so I brought this one out.
It's here, but...
Nothing different about it?
No, not now.
But I did my best.
Rock point now.
Two more questions.
You know what?
Mine.
Here you go.
Balance.
You're doing Kiraco, right?
I did.
It's okay.
No?
Oh, yeah. Raku spac.
I'm going to be zero.
I'm going to get used to it at the bar.
You can't... for now.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I'm sure we all did this.
I'm not sure I'll ever get used to it.
I'm sure they laughed the whole time, but how many times did they laugh?
How many times did you get it?
I've seen so many of these!
I played the market.
The four of us are going on location.
I'm so excited!
Well then...
I want to shoot a TikTok with everyone.
What do you want to do?
I have a favorite dialect.
I'll go do it.
May I?
Momoka-san, senior.
You asked for me.
I trust you.
Like this?
Bamboo crown?
This way.
I don't understand.
My God.
Bamboo crown, then.
Bamboo crown.
Here you go!
Let's do it!
What's that, trust!
That's a joke.
That's a lot of people.
What's that, trust!
Why not?
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good.
I'm shook up
That's good.
I got it
I got it.
You got it, didn't you?
Everyone please check out the official Girls Girls TikTok!
So, without further ado...
If you found this video interesting, please leave a comment and rate it highly!
I'm wearing Bigo's outfit this time!